This peanut butter cup ice cream packs
33 g of protein for just 310 calories,
and it tastes just as good as the real
deal. Let me show you how to make it.
You're going to need your favorite
vanilla protein shake, a little bit of
vanilla bean paste or extract,
sweetener, salt, zantham gum. The full
recipe will be down below in the
description with the exact amounts.
After freezing your pine for at least 16
hours, you can take it out, run under
hot water for 30 seconds to a minute,
and then run it in your Ninja Foodie on
the light ice cream setting. You might
have to respin, but if not, you can grab
your peanut butter cups. I use the mini
Reese's peanut butter cups. Use about
3/4 of a serving in the creamy itself,
ran it on the mixing setting, and then I
topped it with the remaining quarter.
And then if you're feeling really crazy,
you can drizzle some peanut butter on
there, add some peanut butter chips,
some chocolate chips. Literally, the
possibilities are endless.
And all I got to say is that this recipe
is a banger and that if you like peanut
butter, then you have to try it out